{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"answer": 1, "question": "How many sentences are there in this paragraph?", "question_type": 1}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["is", "good", "ram", "dr."]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (3rd person singular present tense).", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["is", "dr.", "ram", "good"]}, {"explanation": "ram is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is ram, Verb (present participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "dr. is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is dr., Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "good is Adjective", "question": "Is good, Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "is is Verb (3rd person singular present tense)", "question": "Is is, Verb (3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "ram is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "dr. _____________ is good .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["authority", "ram", "take-off", "head"]}, {"explanation": "dr. is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ ram is good .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["ram", "capital", "dr.", "authority"]}, {"explanation": "good is Adjective", "question": "Select appropiate Adjective from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "dr. ram is _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["north-eastern", "mobile", "pro", "good"]}], "success": 1}